practiceone.co.uk 2017-06-29

# NameSwitch - switching names made easy

Nameswitch.co.uk is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected and we will not share any of your personal information with third parties. Our privacy policy is set out below. 

* We collect information in 3 ways:

  1. When you provide information directly to us in order to use our service 
  2. When you provide your e-mail address for us to contact you via the contact form on the website 
  3. Through technology such as "cookies" which aggregates non-personally identifiable information on how our website is being used 

Payment for the Nameswitch.co.uk service is enabled via our carefully vetted partner, Stripe. Stripe does not sell or rent your Personal Data to marketers or third parties. Personal Data that is collected by Stripe shall not be retained for longer than is necessary. You can find out more details on Stripe's privacy policy. [**https://stripe.com/gb/privacy**](https://stripe.com/gb/privacy)

* We use the information we collect in the following ways: 

  * To personalise the content of our service, to create your own specific nameswitch.co.uk pack and to contact you regarding your account if required, for instance responding to a query raised by you. 

  * To contact users for marketing purposes, which you can unsubscribe from at any time by simply e-mailing " **Unsubscribe** " to [thegirls@nameswitch.co.uk](mailto:thegirls@nameswitch.co.uk?subject=Unsubscribe&body=Unsubscribe)

  * To improve the content and usability of our services 

The information that we collect and use for any of these purposes shall not be retained for longer than is necessary for those purposes. 

* Nameswitch.co.uk reserves the right to disclose your information to law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties if required by law or we believe in good faith that the disclosure is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss, to report suspected illegal activity, or to investigate violations of our Terms of Service. Any such sharing or disclosure of your information will be in compliance with applicable data protection laws and regulations. 

* "Cookies" are a feature of web browser software that allows web servers to recognise the computer used to access a website. Cookies can remember what information a computer accessed on one web page to streamline activities on related web pages and to make the online experience easier and more personalised. Log files are used to monitor, measure, analyse, improve, and troubleshoot our service. Cookies do not contain any personal information. 

You can opt out of having cookies set on your browser, via your browser's menu. Please note that in doing so it may limit some functionality of our service. 

* We are committed to protecting your information. Your password protects your individual account and you should use a unique and strong password, limit access to your computer and browser, and log out after having used the NameSwitch service. 

We also take all reasonable steps to ensure that the information we collect is stored securely against unauthorised access through the use of various methods including access limitation, and industry-standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology to safeguard the account registration process and sign-up information. Other security safeguards include but are not limited to data encryption, firewalls, and physical access controls to building and files. 

* Occasionally we may change this policy by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. 

When we make material changes, we'll provide you with prominent notice as appropriate under the circumstances, e.g. by displaying a prominent notice within the Service or by sending you an email. Your continued use of the Service after the changes have been made will constitute your acceptance of the changes. 

Questions or comments regarding our privacy policy should be directed to [thegirls@nameswitch.co.uk](mailto:thegirls@nameswitch.co.uk).
